[
  {
    "question": "When was the Playstation 3 released?",
    "choice1": "2006",
    "choice2": "2008",
    "choice3": "2005",
    "choice4": "2012",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What color does yellow and green make?",
    "choice1": "Ocean mist",
    "choice2": "Lime ",
    "choice3": "Maroon",
    "choice4": "Tangerine",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "who is the youngest person to receive a nobel prize?",
    "choice1": "Tasuku Honjo",
    "choice2": "Paul Romer",
    "choice3": "Malala Yousafzai",
    "choice4": "Michael Rosbash",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "MS-Word is an example of _____",
    "choice1": "An operating system",
    "choice2": "A processing device",
    "choice3": "An input device",
    "choice4": "Application software",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "A computer cannot 'boot' if it does not have the _____",
    "choice1": "Operating system",
    "choice2": "Compiler",
    "choice3": "Loader",
    "choice4": "Assembler",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The purest form of iron is",
    "choice1": "steel",
    "choice2": "wrought iron ",
    "choice3": "pig iron",
    "choice4": "nickel steel",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Junk e-mail is also called ______",
    "choice1": "Spoof",
    "choice2": "Sniffer script",
    "choice3": "Spam",
    "choice4": "Spool",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Hydrogen bomb is based on the principle of",
    "choice1": "nuclear fission",
    "choice2": "artificial radioactivity",
    "choice3": "natural radioactivity",
    "choice4": "nuclear fusion",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The blue colour of the clear sky is due to",
    "choice1": "Reflection of light",
    "choice2": "Diffraction of light",
    "choice3": "Dispersion of light",
    "choice4": "Refraction of light",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which foreign country is closest to Andaman Islands",
    "choice1": "Sri Lanka",
    "choice2": "Indonesia",
    "choice3": "Pakistan",
    "choice4": "Myanmar",
    "answer": 4
  }
]
